Guide to the Papers of Simon Dubnow (1860-1941) 1589-1938, 1961 (bulk 1700-1900) RG 87
Center for Jewish History, Publisher.
- Series VII: Letters to Dubnow, 1885-1931, 1961; 26 folders
  - Kuf ק, 1888-1898 (Folder 1030, Item 77491-77516)
    Moshe Kalmasohn, (2), 1888-1889
    Yosef Kantortshik, (1), 1896
    Ben-Tsion Katz, Dobre, (1), 1894
    A. Kraushar, Warsaw, (1), 1896
    Hirsh Krasnik, Petropavlovsk, (1), 1898
    Koszycki, Ostroh, (1), 1896
    M. Kreynin, Moscow, (2), 1894
    Fadya M. Kreynin, Kritshev, Mohilever Gubernia, (1), 1895
  - Resh ר, 1892-1903, 1931 (Folder 1031, Item 77517-77527)
    M. Rabinovich, Jerusalem, (1), 5691 (1931)
    Shalom Rabinovich (Sholem Aleichem), Odessa, (1), 1892
    Sha'ul B. Rabinovich, Pinsk, (1), 1903
    A. R. Rosenthal, Vilna, (1), 1895
    Ber-Leib (Dov-Yehudah) Rasin, (2), 1892
    Emanuel Ringelblum, Warsaw, (1), no date
    Ben-Tsion, Vorovel, (1), 1892
  - Shin ש, 1891-1910, 1928-1932 (Folder 1032, Item 77528-77558)
    Dr. Moshe Schorr, Vienna, (3), 1900
    Avraham Szwadron, Jerusalem, (2), 1928-1932
    Simhe Scherzer, Zhadove, (1), 1931
    S. L. Shneyerson, Warsaw (3), 1891-1893
    Ya'akov Shapiro, Mezrich, (4), 1892
    Shefer, Rasin, (1), 1904
    L. Sklar, 1910
    L. Shulman, Kiev, (1), 1893
  - Unidentified letters, undated (Folder 1033, Item 77559-77566)
    also documents sent along with letters
  - Various materials about Dubnow collected by Riva Tcherikower, 1916, undated (Folder 1034, Item 77567-77646)
    including:
    permission for temporary residence in Finland, 1916
    Dubnow celebrations
    Dubnow exhibits
  - Various materials about Dubnow collected by Riva Tcherikower, 1961 (Folder 1035, Item 77647-77749)
    catalogues of Dubnow exhibits at YIVO
  - Various materials about Dubnow collected by Riva Tcherikower, undated (Folder 1036, Item 77750-77833)
    news clippings about Dubnow
  - Copies of letters from S. Dubnow, undated (Folder 1037, Item 77834-77905)
    Yosef Opatoshu
    Leon Baratz
    G. Binshtok
    Dina Garfinkel
    Reel 80
  - Copies of letters from S. Dubnow, undated (Folder 1038, Item 77906-77924)
    Max Weinreich (also some from Weinreich)
    to M. Vishniak
    Chaim Zhitlowsky
    L. Chazanovitsh
    S. Dingol
    L. Toybsh
  - Copies of letters from S. Dubnow, undated (Folder 1039, Item 77925-77986)
    Daniel Charney
  - Copies of letters from S. Dubnow, undated (Folder 1040, Item 77987-78069)
    the Jewish Youth Library in Rio de Janeiro
    the J. National Workers (Labor) Farband (later known as Labor-Zionist Alliance)
    Nathan Chanin (at the Arbeter Ring)
    V. Latsky
    Shmuel Lifshitz
    Jacob Lestchinsky
  - Copies of letters from S. Dubnow, undated (Folder 1041, Item 78070-78163)
    David Movshovitsh
  - Copies of letters from S. Dubnow, undated (Folder 1042, Item 78164-78198)
    M. Sudarsky
    Bertha Emanuel
    the Peretz-Society, New York
    Fridlander
    L. Koenig
    Shim’on Rabinovitsh
    S. Rosenfeld
    Y. Rayzman
    S. Reznik
    Shapiro, of Der Tog
  - Copies of letters from S. Dubnow, undated (Folder 1043, Item 78199-78269)
    Ya’akov Shatzky
    Yitzhak N. Shteynberg
    correspondence regarding distribution of the book Yidishe Geshikhte far Kinder (History of the Jews for Children) with Lipe Lehrer and Elias Tcherikower